https://ccneedham.org/privacy

Christ Church Episcopal NeedhamFacebookYouTubeMembersLiturgical CustomaryNewslettersPoliciesRegistration FormsHow Firm a Foundation: Our Annual Appeal for 2021HomeCalendarContact UsWelcomeRector’s WelcomeOur ChurchOur Community LifeOur LeadershipOur FaithVisiting?WorshipServicesSermonsMusicBaptismsWeddingsFuneralsLearningChildren’s ProgramChildren’s Chapel and Church SchoolConfirmationYouth GroupAdult EducationServingGetting InvolvedCommunity Art GalleryGreen TeamLocal OutreachYouth Mission TripsHaiti PartnershipPastoral CareSharing our ResourcesGivingTime and TalentFinancial SupportCar DonationOur Privacy PolicyPlease read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.What does this Privacy Policy cover?This Privacy Policy covers Christ Episcopal Church’s treatment of personally identifiable information that you share with us. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.What personal information does Christ Episcopal Church gather?The information we learn from you will help us personalize and continually improve your experience at ccneedham.org. Here are the types of information we gather.Information You Give UsWe receive and store information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our Web site features. We use the information that you provide to assist us in responding to your requests, and communicating with you.E-mailTo help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Christ Church if your computer supports this capability.What are cookies?Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide certain features to you during your visits.At this time, we are not using cookies on our website. If we choose to add cookies to our site in the future, their purpose will be explicitly identified in this policy. When you login to our member pages, you will be given the option to “Remember Me” on the login screen. This places a login cookie from Access ACS on your computer. If you don’t check the box, the cookie is not stored.Does Christ Church share the information it receives?Information about you is for the sole purpose of providing you the web services you request and will never be shared outside this organization. The Episcopal ChurchChrist Episcopal Church, Needham 1132 Highland Ave., Needham, MA 02494 · 781-444-1469Contact Us · Map & Directions · Privacy Policy · Sitemap · Login © Copyright 2017 Episcopal Diocese of Massachusetts
